<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<!-- Settings -->
	
	<Bloodmoon_raidModifier>Multiplier for the number of werewolves that spawn during a raid.</Bloodmoon_raidModifier>
	<Bloodmoon_minTicksPerEvent>Minimum ticks per werewolf raid during a bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_minTicksPerEvent>
	<Bloodmoon_maxTicksPerEvent>Maximum ticks per werewolf raid during a bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_maxTicksPerEvent>
	<Bloodmoon_extraAvatarChance>Chance of additional avatars of Hircine spawning when a bloodmoon raid occurs.</Bloodmoon_extraAvatarChance>
	<Bloodmoon_infectionChance>Chance of a werewolf attack infecting the target.</Bloodmoon_infectionChance>
	<Bloodmoon_minNumberOfLootDrops>Minimum number of loot drops that will spawn at the end of a bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_minNumberOfLootDrops>
	<Bloodmoon_maxNumberOfLootDrops>Maximum number of loot drops that will spawn at the end of a bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_maxNumberOfLootDrops>
	<Bloodmoon_enableBloodmoonForAll>Enable the rogue bloodmoon event for all storytellers. Note that it will not occur on a cycle.</Bloodmoon_enableBloodmoonForAll>
	<Bloodmoon_enableMessages>Enable messages for werewolf raids during a bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_enableMessages>
	<Bloodmoon_chanceOfGiftedWerewolf>Chance a werewolf spawned during a bloodmoon will spawn with a gift of Hircine.</Bloodmoon_chanceOfGiftedWerewolf>
	<Bloodmoon_enableLootDrops>Enable loot drops at the end of a bloodmoon, assuming anyone is left alive.</Bloodmoon_enableLootDrops>
	<Bloodmoon_enableBloodmoonCycleForAll>Enable the bloodmoon cycle for all storytellers.</Bloodmoon_enableBloodmoonCycleForAll>
	
	<Bloodmoon_enableMarking>Enable wild animals becoming marked during the bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_enableMarking>
	<Bloodmoon_minTicksPerMark>Minimum ticks per marked animal during a bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_minTicksPerMark>
	<Bloodmoon_maxTicksPerMark>Maximum ticks per marked animal during a bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_maxTicksPerMark>
	
	<Bloodmoon_elixirFailChance>Chance for consuming a lycanthropic elixir to fail.</Bloodmoon_elixirFailChance>
	
	<Bloodmoon_minWerewolfNum>The minimum number of werewolves that can spawn in a bloodmoon raid.</Bloodmoon_minWerewolfNum>
	<Bloodmoon_maxWerewolfNum>The maximum number of werewolves that can spawn in a bloodmoon raid.</Bloodmoon_maxWerewolfNum>
	
	<Bloodmoon_werewolfStrength>Modifier for the strength of werewolves, a higher number means stronger werewolves.</Bloodmoon_werewolfStrength>
	
	<Bloodmoon_incidentIntervalCycle>Minimum number of days until the bloodmoon cycle event can occur again.</Bloodmoon_incidentIntervalCycle>
	<Bloodmoon_incidentIntervalRogue>Minimum number of days until the rogue bloodmoon event can occur again.</Bloodmoon_incidentIntervalRogue>
	
	<Bloodmoon_incidentMinimumDaysCycle>Minimum number if days until the bloodmoon cycle event can occur.</Bloodmoon_incidentMinimumDaysCycle>
	<Bloodmoon_incidentMinimumDaysRogue>Minimum number if days until the rogue bloodmoon event can occur.</Bloodmoon_incidentMinimumDaysRogue>
	
	<Bloodmoon_enableWerewolfPack>Enable the werewolf pack quest.</Bloodmoon_enableWerewolfPack>
	
	<Bloodmoon_enableLetters>Enable letters for werewolf raids during a bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_enableLetters>
	<Bloodmoon_huntersGiftMaximum>The maximum buildup for hunters gifts obtained through a totem.</Bloodmoon_huntersGiftMaximum>
	<Bloodmoon_huntersGiftBuildup>The percentage buildup towards a hunters gift obtained from a single totem.</Bloodmoon_huntersGiftBuildup>
	
	<Bloodmoon_enableStrengthScaling>Enable the strength of werewolves increasing with each subsequent bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_enableStrengthScaling>
	<Bloodmoon_enableStrengthScalingTooltip>Each time a bloodmoon, from any source, ends, the strength of new werewolves will be permanently increased by 10%, up to a maximum of 100%.\n\nThe strength modifier setting sets the initial value if it is above 0%\n\nThis setting is not retroactive, enabling it after surviving several bloodmoons will start werewolves at the default value.</Bloodmoon_enableStrengthScalingTooltip>
	
	<Bloodmoon_enableBloodmoonAmbushes>Enable werewolf caravan ambushes during a bloodmoon.</Bloodmoon_enableBloodmoonAmbushes>
	
	<Bloodmoon_enableBloodmoonTracker>Enable the bloodmoon tracker alert.</Bloodmoon_enableBloodmoonTracker>
	
	<Bloodmoon_default>Reset to default values</Bloodmoon_default>
	<Bloodmoon_classic>Use classic settings</Bloodmoon_classic>
	<Bloodmoon_classicTooltip>Change the current settings to something closer to the classic MorrowRim - Bloodmoon experience.\n\nBloodmoon are frequent, and Hircine's hounds are endless.</Bloodmoon_classicTooltip>

	<!-- Pages -->
	
	<Bloodmoon_PageBasic>Basic Settings</Bloodmoon_PageBasic>
	<Bloodmoon_PageBloodmoon>Bloodmoon Balance Settings</Bloodmoon_PageBloodmoon>
	<Bloodmoon_PageLycanthropy>Lycanthropy Settings</Bloodmoon_PageLycanthropy>
	
	<!-- Messages -->
	
	<Bloodmoon_LetterLabelwerewolvesAppear>werewolf pack sighted</Bloodmoon_LetterLabelwerewolvesAppear>	
	<Bloodmoon_werewolvesAppear>Your colonists hear howling in the distance; Hircine's hounds have been let loose.</Bloodmoon_werewolvesAppear>	
	<Bloodmoon_animalMarked>Hircine has marked {0}, and wishes for you to hunt it.</Bloodmoon_animalMarked>	
	<Bloodmoon_animalLostMarked>{0} is no longer marked for the hunt.</Bloodmoon_animalLostMarked>	
	
	<Bloodmoon_capacityMaxed>{0} has already fully upgraded {1}</Bloodmoon_capacityMaxed>
	
	<Bloodmoon_houndsFactionNotFound>The Hounds of Hircine faction was not found, preventing the {0}. Please generate the missing faction using the Vanilla Expanded Framework.</Bloodmoon_houndsFactionNotFound>

	<Bloodmoon_LetterLabelstrengthScaling>Hounds strengthened</Bloodmoon_LetterLabelstrengthScaling>
	<Bloodmoon_strengthScalingMessage>Hircine has strengthened his hounds to {0}%. They will now be a greater threat when next encountered.</Bloodmoon_strengthScalingMessage>

	<Bloodmoon_bloodmoonDescription>During the bloodmoon avatars of Hircine may appear around the map. Hunting these can grant your colonists permanent buffs. Beware though, as during a bloodmoon you will not always be the hunter.\n\nThe bloodmoon rising will activate any cases of dormant lycanthropy, permanently turning the victim into a rabid werewolf.\n\nThe current strength scaling for werewolves is {0}%</Bloodmoon_bloodmoonDescription>
	
	<!-- Alerts -->

	<Bloodmoon_Alert_TrackerLabel>Bloodmoon tracker</Bloodmoon_Alert_TrackerLabel>
	<Bloodmoon_Alert_BloodmoonTrackerDescription>Next bloodmoon expected in {0} days.</Bloodmoon_Alert_BloodmoonTrackerDescription>
	<Bloodmoon_Alert_WerewolfTrackerDescription>Hircine's Hounds will grow stronger with each bloodmoon you survive, gaining increased resistances and capacities.\n\nThis strength increase not only affects the werewolves encountered during bloodmoon, but also the werewolves encountered in pack hunt quests.\n\nCurrent strength is {0}%</Bloodmoon_Alert_WerewolfTrackerDescription>
	
</LanguageData>